const data = [
  {
     id: 1, 
     question: 'JSX stands for what?', 
     answer: 'JavaScript XML'
   }, 
   {
     id: 2, 
     question: 'Which of the following concepts is/are key to ReactJS?', 
     answer: 'Both of the above',

   }, 
   {
     id: 3, 
     question: 'What are the life cycles of ReactJS?', 
     answer: 'All of these'
   }, 
   {
     id: 4, 
     question: 'Which of the following is used to pass the data from parent to child?', 
     answer: 'State'
   }, 
   {
     id: 5, 
     question: 'How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?', 
     answer: "this.values"
   }, 
   {
     id: 6,
     question: ' What is a good use case for using a function while rendering a dynamic list of items?', 
     answer: 'A. If we need to compute a value based on the properties of items in the loop.', 
   }, 
   {
     id: 7, 
     question: 'What is the second argument for setState useful for?', 
     answer: 'A. To invoke code after the setState operation is done.'
   }, 
   {
   id: 9, 
   question: 'ReactJS uses _________ to increase performance.', 
   answer: 'Virtual DOM', 
   }, 
   {
     id: 10, 
     question: 'What is the default port for webpack dev server?', 
     answer: '8080'
   }, 
   {
     id: 11, 
     question: 'What are two ways data gets handled in react?', 
     answer: 'state & props'
   }, 
   {
     id: 12, 
     question: 'React Js is developed by Facebook?', 
     answer: 'Facebook'
   }, 
   {
     id: 13, 
     question: 'What are the limitations of ReactJS?', 
     answer: 'All of these'
   }, 
   {
     id: 14, 
     question: 'How many stages are there in React js life cycle?', 
     answer: '3'
   },
   {
     id: 15, 
     question: 'In relation to React JS component lifecycle, which statement is true?', 
     answer: 'B. Only Class components can have a life cycle.'
   }, 
   {
     id: 16, 
     question: 'In react, this is used to pass data to component from outside?', 
     answer: 'props'
   }, 
   {
     id: 17, 
     question: 'Ref in react component us used to assign reference to DOM elements. Ref can be created by_____?', 
     answer: 'C. Both of above'
   }, 
   {
     id: 18, 
     question: 'Everything in React is a ____?', 
     answer: 'Component'
   }, 
   {
     id: 19, 
     question: 'Which of the following is a correct definition of state in react?', 
     answer: 'B. An internal data store (object) of component'
 }, 
 {
   id: 20, 
   question: 'The state in React can be updated by call to setState method. These calls are ____?', 
   answer: 'Asynchronous in nature'
 }, 
 {
   id: 21, 
   question: 'Keys are given to a list of elements in react. These keys should be____?', 
   answer: 'B. Unique among the siblings only'
 }, 
 {
   id: 22, 
   question: 'React is a _________?', 
   answer: 'JavaScript library'
 }, 
 {
   id: 23, 
   question: 'Props in react can _______ ?', 
   answer: 'Not be changed in '
 }, 
 {
 id: 24, 
 question: 'In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?', 
 answer: 'Extends'
 }, 
 {
   id: 25, 
   question: 'Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?', 
   answer: 'D. super()'
 }, {
   id: 26, 
   question: 'What are the two main ways of creating a component in React?', 
   answer: 'Class-based and Functional'
 }, 
 {
   id: 27, 
   question: 'What is the definition of a Function Component?', 
   answer: 'B. A JavaScript function that takes a props argument and returns a React element.'
 }
]
export default data